Hello, my name is Sajeev, an army retired
person. Watch this video till the end. It will be
a good experience for you. The
reason for making such a video is a
small experience that happened recently.
This incident happened
between 12 am and 1 am. My
son had a medical issue and had to
go to the hospital at night.
There, I happened to see a father and mother, aged between 60 and 65, for
treatment. The mother's
condition was very sad. She had serious
health issues. She had no
relatives or relatives with her. She did
not have any money or health insurance cards in her hand. I
asked her about her condition and asked her to give me some money.
But since that money was not enough for the treatment, she had to leave it at the
hospital. Since
my son was admitted,
I could not give a lot of money.
Seeing that, I felt very sad. Seeing this situation,
I was inspired to make such a video.
I am saying this from an idea of ​​mine.
We should calculate life in three parts, from
one year to
25 years.  We earn money with our parents and
after that by doing our own job or
business. We should
have the knowledge to invest that money in a way that benefits us. After the age of 50,
due to the changes in our health, we have to
use a good amount of savings for it. That's when
we realize the disadvantages of not taking a health policy and not making the
right
investments.
We
recognize that for that, we choose good
investments and health policies.
ICICI's health
policy and life policy are the
best examples of that. The risk is zero%.
We all know that ICICI is an international bank. So,
you can only imagine the profit made in investments. Then,
all the products you choose should
be profitable. It would be good for you to
seek the opinion of a good advisor when making any investment. I did
not have much knowledge.
I
got the best knowledge through each class at ICICI. There are many good
plans. We will try to
bring them to you gradually through each video.
You must have heard it in every home.  It is
not him or her who is
responsible for the losses we have suffered because of her. We are the only ones who are responsible for it. It
happened because of our ignorance. When investing,
do it after knowing everything.
Choose only products that make profit. Remember that if you go for a lot of profit,
you will end up in a lot of loss.
Therefore, if you are
interested in investing or taking health plans,
call the mobile number shown here and we will explain and explain the
best investment plans. This is the
first
video I am posting. If you like it, don't forget to
subscribe and like it. If there is
any
mistake, I apologize. See you again with another
good investment plan and health
plans.